Register of the Milton Friedman papers 77011.4088897
Hoover Institution Archives
- Audio-Visual File, 1969-1988 (Boxes 102-107)
  - Economics Cassette Series sound recordings, 1968-1978; 207.0 Cassettes (Boxes 103-107)
    - 127. "Monetary Policy and Inflation, Foreign Influences On Money Supply,", 1973 August 15; 31:22 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005799
    - 128. "Controlling Money Supply, Monetary Growth, Leading Indications, Prime Rate,", 1973 August 29; 28:01 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005800
    - 129. "Monetary Developments, Tax Increase, Foreign Influences on Inflation, Export Controls,", 1973 September 13; 28:01 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005801
    - 130. "Short Term Rates, Business Outlook, Hedging Against Inflation,", 1973 September 26; 29:11 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005802
    - 131. "Oil, Government Business Relations,", 1973 October 10; 26:54 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005803
    - 132. "Watergate and Economics, Control of Money, Ludwig von Mises,", 1973 October 24; 27:06 (Box 105)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005804
    - 133. "Money Supply, Burns' Comments, California Amendment,", 1973 November 7; 26:53 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005832
    - 134. "Oil Crisis and the Stock Market, Business Prospects, Long Term Oil Problems, Two-Tier Gold System,", 1973 November 21; 24:36 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005833
    - 135. "Oil Crisis, Stock Market, Burns' Letter on Monetary Policy,", 1973 December 4; 26:59 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005834
    - 136. "Economic Outlook for 1974,", 1973 December 13; 27:21 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005835
    - 137. "Brazilian Economic Miracle,", 1974 January 4; 27:14 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005836
    - 138. "Economic Conditions, Monetary Policy, International Scene, Watergate and Resignation,", 1974 January 16; 26:31 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005837
    - 139. "Recession?, Monetary Policy,", 1974 February 4; 26:16 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005838
    - 140. "Personal Income and Wholesale Prices, Real Money Balances, Monetary Correction,", 1974 February 20; 30:02 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005839
    - 141. "British Election, Escalator Clauses,", 1974 March 12; 26:54 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005840
    - 142. "President Nixon, Money, Inflation,", 1974 March 20; 26:51 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005841
    - 143. "French and British Situation, US Economic Situation,", 1974 April 3; 27:35 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005842
    - 144. "Money, Disintermediation, Thrift Institutions, Inflation Prospects,", 1974 April 17; 30:17 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005843
    - 145. "Money Figures and Fed Stand, Nixon-Burns Forecast About Food/Fuel 'Bubble Burst Effect,'", 1974 May 1; 30:37 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005847
    - 146. "Franklin National, Flexible Exchange Rates, Ideas vs. Experience,", 1974 May 20; 32:06 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005848
    - 147. "Monetary Policy, Burns' Talk, Leading Indicators, Wage Price Controls,", 1974 May 30; 33:24 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005894
    - 148. "Monetary Policy, Trade With Soviet Union, Euro-Dollar, Interest Rates,", 1974 June 11; 30:01 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005895
    - 149. "Current Economic Conditions, Capital Markets, Indexation Stock Volume and Prices,", 1974 June 26; 26:49 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005896
    - 150. "Alan Greenspan, Monetary Growth, Recession?, Bank Failures,", 1974 July 24; 31:22 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005897
    - 151. "Implications of Prospective End of Nixon Presidency, Retrospective on Nixon Years, Commercial and Industrial Loans,", 1974 August 7; 33:20 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005900
    - 152. "Monetary Policy, Economic Prospects, GM and Ford Price Hikes, Price and Wage Controls?,", 1974 August 21; 30:52 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005901
    - 153. "Pre-Summit Meeting of Economists,", 1974 September 6; 28:07 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005902
    - 154. "Second Pre-Summit Meeting of Economists, Europe,", 1974 September 24; 28:43 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0005903
    - 155. "President Ford's Message,", 1974 October 10; 29:04 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006588
    - 156. "Prospects for Inflation, Business Conditions, Interest Rates, British Election,", 1974 October 23; 28:11 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006589
    - 157. "Election Consequences, Media, Money Supply,", 1974 November 6; 26:13 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006590
    - 158. "Current Economic Conditions, Leading Indicators, Real Money Balances,", 1974 November 19; 26:13 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006591
    - 159. "Economic Outlook for 1975,", 1974 December; 27:05 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006592
    - 160. "Steel Prices, Personal Income, Money and Prices, Administration Policy,", 1974 December 19; 28:04 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006593
    - 161. "Gold, Economist's News, Ford's State of Union Message, Monetary Policy, Mundell Proposal,", 1975 January 1; 25:15 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006594
    - 162. "State of the Union,", 1975 January; 26:55 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006595
    - 163. "Budget, Money Supply, Edward Leir, Reuss and Proxmire,", 1975 February, number 1; 26:55 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006614
    - 164. "Unemployment, Monetary Policy, Humphrey-Proxmire Resolution, 1975 February, number 2; 28:03 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006615
    - 165. "Readers' Questions, Oil Cartel,", 1975 February; 28:03 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006616
    - 166. "Travel Plans, Monetary Policy, Railroads,", 1975 March; 27:52 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006617
    - 167. "Domestic Economy, Vacuum In Far East, Chile Inflation,", 1975 May; 25:58 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006618
    - 168. "Money, Energy,", 1975 June; 20:19 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006619
    - 169. "Money Watch, Weakening of British Pound, Rebate Impact,", 1975 June; 20:44 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006620
    - 170. "Economic and Monetary Developments,", 1975 June; 20:13 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006621
    - 171. "Unemployment Now, Unemployment in the 30s, 'Crowding Out,' Federal Debt, Australia,", 1975 July; 29:58 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006622
    - 172. "Inflation, Monetary Policy, Interest Rates, Unemployment,", 1975 July; 24:33 (Box 106)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006623
    - 173. "Monetary Policy, Wheat Sale, Oil Decontrol, Kelso,", 1975 August; 27:42 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006626
    - 174. "Inflation, Federal Debt, Anemic Expansion,", 1975 August; 27:23 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006627
    - 175. "Money, Federal Reserve Bank of San Francisco, Monetary Targets, Eurodollars,", 1975 September; 30:19 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006628
    - 176. "Monetary Watch, Economic Jitters, Tax Reduction,", 1975 September; 23:59 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006629
    - 177. "Leading Indicators, OPEC, Interest Rates,", 1975 October; 25:31 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006697
    - 178. "Presidents Ford's Tax Program, New York City, Monetary Policy,", 1975 October; 23:54 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006698
    - 179. "Chile, 1976 Economic Conditions, Prime Rate, Monetary Policy,", 1975 October; 26:33 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006787
    - 180. "Monetary Testimony, Australia, Corporation Taxes,", 1975 November; 25:07 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006788
    - 181. "Outlook for 1976,", 1975 November; 27:59 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006789
    - 182. "Monetary Situation, Interest Rates, Taxes, Labor, Negotiations,", 1975 December; 25:43 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006790
    - 183. "T-Bill Futures Market, Evans Predictions, Monetarism,", 1976 January; 27:16 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006791
    - 184. "State of Union, IMF, Interest Rates,", 1976 January; 30:12 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006792
    - 188. "French Franc, Gold and South Africa, Monetary Developments, Comment on Dr. Hayek's Speech,", 1976 March; 31:45 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006793
    - 189. "Current Economic Conditions, Southern Africa,", 1976 April; 32:21 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006794
    - 190. "Monetary Developments, Fed, Targets, 'The Interest Rate,' Floating Rates, British Wage Agreement,", 1976 May; 31:16 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006795
    - 191. "Money, Inventories, Communists in Italy,", 1976 May; 29:15 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006796
    - 192. "British Pound, Prices and Employment, Interest Rate, Can the Corporation Survive?,", 1976 June; 30:17 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006797
    - 193. "British Pound, Domestic Economy, Business Week Article,", 1965 June; 29:39 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006798
    - 194. "Summit Meeting, Money Figures, Silver for Sugar, Subscribers' Letters,", 1976 June; 26:01 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006799
    - 195. "Money, Inflation, Interest Rates and Stock Prices,", 1976 July; 25:48 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006800
    - 196. "Monetary Targets, Natural Gas Prices, Monetarism in Britain,", 1976 July; 29:22 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006801
    - 197. "Economics and Monetary Development, Talk by Henry Kaufman, Investment Tax Credit, Swine Flu,", 1976 August; 29:38 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006802
    - 198. "Current Economic Situation, U.K. Economy, Rolls Royce, Money and Prices, New Hampshire and Vermont Taxes,", 1976 September; 30:16 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006803
    - 199. "Money, French Price Control, Mexican Peso, Bond and Stock Yields,", 1976 September; 29:56 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006804
    - 200. "British Pound, Leading Indications, Weekly Money Supply, M1 and M2 Velocity,", 1976 October; 28:40 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006805
    - 201. "Nobel Prize, Ford-Carter Economics, GNP and Monetary Policy,", 1976 October; 27:53 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006806
    - 202. "The Election,", 1976 November; 27:27 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006807
    - 203. "Carter's Press Conference, International Situation, Canada and Separatism, Money and Investment,", 1976 November; 23:34 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006808
    - 204. "Economic Outlook for 1977,", 1976 December; 33:35 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006809
    - 205. "Nobel Ceremonies, Nobel Lecture, Tax Cut,", 1976 December; 31:10 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006810
    - 206. "Change in Tone, Carter Program, Subscribers' Questions,", 1977 January; 31:02 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006814
    - 207. "Monetary Policy, Carter Program, Energy, Business and Free Enterprise,", 1977 January; 29:33 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006815
    - 208. "Monetary Growth, Burns' Testimony, Reuss Letter, Rationing Water,", 1977 February; 31:30 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006820
    - 209. "The Fed, Carter Dispute, Burns' Reappointment, Rebate, Mexico,", 1977 March; 30:13 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006821
    - 210. "Monetary and Economic Developments, Legislation on Taxes, British Budget, TV Tariffs, Mexico,", 1977 March; 24:40 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006827
    - 211. "Carter Withdrawal of Refund, Monetary Policy, Energy, Employment,", 1977 April; 25:52 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006828
    - 212. "Energy, Canadian Dollar, Monetary Restriction and Inflation,", 1977 April; 28:48 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006829
    - 213. "Social Security Proposals, Steel Prices, Fed Chairmanship, Kristol Article,", 1977 May; 35:10 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006830
    - 214. "General Economic Conditions, Alaska, Israel,", 1977 May; 30:23 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006835
    - 215. "Swan Song,", 1978 January; 31:40 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0006836
      The Friedmans conclude the Economics Cassette Series by previewing Milton's upcoming video lecture series and the Free to Choose television program. Following this, Milton gives his economic outlook.
    - Unnumbered sound recording, 1969 January 6 (Box 107)
      Use copy reference number: 77011_a_0002446
      The program is of Paul A. Samuelson alone, commenting on the United States economy at the beginning of 1969 as the Johnson administration leaves Washington and Nixon takes office. Milton Friedman is not on the cassette. Both sides have the same program. The cassette has "Paul A. Samuelson" written on both sides.
- Charts used in Monetary Trends in the U.S. and the United Kingdom, 1982 (Box 108)
- Photographs, 1975-1978 (Photo file)
  Three photographic prints depicting Milton Friedman during his appearances on the television program Meet the Press in 1976 and 1978; 2 prints depicting him with others in 1978; and 1 print depicting him with James McClune and Joseph Pichler following his talk in Kansas City, Missouri, on December 4, 1975.
- Incremental Materials, General, 1931-2006 (Boxes 109-112)
  Materials collected between 1984-2007, including notes, drafts, writings, oversize photographs and certificates showing award of honorary degrees, videocassettes, and photocopies of all Wall Street Journal and Newsweek columns written.
  - Correspondence, Leontief, W. W., 1936 (Box-folder 109: 1)
  - University of Chicago, Wesley Claire Mitchell Research Professorship, 1961 (Box-folder 109: 2)
  - Social Security research materials, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 109: 3)
  - Notes on published articles, circa 1931-1935 (Box-folder 109: 4)
  - National Resources Committee, 1936 (Box-folder 109: 5)
  - "Retrospective Analysis of the Inflationary Gap for Calendar Year 1942," Treasury Department, Tax Research Division (Box-folder 109: 6)
  - "Regression Analysis of Family Expenditure Data," National Bureau of Economic Research, undated (Box-folder 109: 7)
  - Notes, drafts, statistics, circa 1954 (Box-folder 109: 8)
  - "Consumption and Family Expenditures," notes, drafts, statistics, 1950s (Box-folder 109: 9)
  - "Consumption," statistics, results, and correspondence, 1954-1956 (Box-folder 109: 10)
  - "Theory of Consumption Function,", undated (Box-folder 109: 11)
  - Draft fragments, undated (Box-folder 109: 12)
  - Photographs, 1940s-1991, undated.
    General note
    See also Photo file and boxes 113-115
    - 1940s-1950s (Box-folder 109: 13)
    - 1960s (Box-folder 109: 14)
    - 1970s (Box-folder 109: 15)
    - Nobel Prize, 1976 (Box-folder 109: 16)
    - 1980s (Box-folder 109: 17)
    - Nobel Prize Jubilee, 1991 (Box-folder 109: 18)
    - Undated (Box-folder 109: 19)
  - Coursework and exams, 1948, undated (Box-folder 109: 20)
  - Charts, undated (Box-folder 109: 21)
  - Hearings on the 1951 Annual Economic Report (Box-folder 109: 22)
  - "Probability and the Attempts to Measure Utility" draft by Paul Samuelson, circa 1948 (Box-folder 109: 23)
  - Newsweek column response letters, 1976 (Box-folder 109: 24)
  - Printed matter by Harry Schultz, 1933, 1935, undated (Box-folder 109: 25)
  - Printed matter on economics, 1944-1977 (Box-folder 109: 26)
  - Vermont home brochure, undated (Box-folder 109: 27)
  - White House Fellows certificate, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 109: 28)
  - Oversize photographs, 1971-1997
    See also Photo file and boxes 109, 113-115
    - With Richard Nixon, 1971 June (Box-folder 110: 1)
      Signed photograph and certificate.
    - Free to Choose television program, circa 1979 (Box-folder 110: 2)
    - Mont Pélerin Society meeting groups, 1987, 1990, 1997 (Box-folder 110: 3)
  - Oversize materials, 1945-1981
    - U.S. Dept. of Commerce sample forms, 1945 (Box-folder 110: 4)
    - Time magazine cover, 1969 (Box-folder 110: 5)
    - Honorary Doctorate, Universidad Francisco Marroquín, Guatemala, photographs, clippings, and other materials, 1978 (Box-folder 110: 6)
    - Clippings, 1947-1976 (Box-folder 110: 7)
    - U.S. President's Policy Board certificate, 1981 (Box-folder 110: 8)
  - VHS video cassettes (Box 111)
    - "A Conversation with Milton Friedman," Institute of Government Affairs, undated
    - "Milton Friedman on Dinah Shore," KBHK SFO California, 1977 March 3
    - "Tyranny of the Status Quo,", 1983 November 4
    - "Health Care Reform: A Conversation between Milton Friedman and Alain Enthoven," Palmer R. Chitester Fund, Inc., 1992
    - "Money: Milton Friedman, Robert Hall, Daniel Gressel," Palmer R. Chitester Fund, Inc., 1992
    - "Monetary Revolutions: Milton Friedman, Robert Hall, Daniel Gressel," Palmer R. Chitester Fund, Inc., 1992
    - "Preference, Self-Interest, Subtle Choices," Gary Becker and Aaron Wildavsky, Palmer R. Chitester Fund, Inc., 1993
    - "Damn Right," produced by John K. Andrews, Jr. and Robert J. Chitester, 1995
    - "Transition in Eastern Europe and Consumer Behavior," Ronald Coase and Gary Becker, Palmer R. Chitester Fund, Inc., 1995
    - "Cato Institute Twentieth Anniversary Dinner,", circa 1997
    - "NTU Talks with Milton Friedman,", 1999 Spring
    - "Uncommon Knowledge: A Presidential Report Card, Milton Friedman on the State of the Union,", 1999 May 22
    - "Uncommon Knowledge: Take it to the Limits, Milton Friedman on Libertarianism,", 1999 May 15
  - Mont Pélerin Society, general meeting papers, 1982 (Box-folder 112: 1)
  - Wall Street Journal opinions and editorials (photocopies), 1961-2006 (Box-folder 112: 2)
  - Newsweek columns (photocopies), 1966-1984 (Box-folder 112: 3)
- Incremental Photographs, 1930s-2002 (Boxes 113-115)
  Photographs of events, trips, and meetings, as well as press release and publicity photos.
  - Offices at the University of Chicago and Stanford University, undated (Box-folder 113: 1)
  - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith, undated (Box-folder 113: 2)
  - Wall Street Week, television program, undated (Box-folder 113: 3)
  - Milton Friedman essay contest winners, seventh annual, Stanford University, undated (Box-folder 113: 4)
  - Milton Friedman portraits, 1930-1980 (Box-folder 113: 5-8)
  - Photographs from Oriental Economist, 1934-1990 (Box-folder 113: 9)
  - Treasury Department, 1941-1943 (Box-folder 113: 10)
  - France, 1950 (Box-folder 113: 11)
  - Wabash, 1957 (Box-folder 113: 12)
  - Tokyo, 1962 (Box-folder 113: 13)
  - Chicago Sun-Times, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 113: 14)
  - Israel, 1969 (Box-folder 113: 15)
  - Expo-70, Japan, 1970 (Box-folder 113: 16)
  - Milton Friedman on a farm, 1971 (Box-folder 113: 17)
  - Nobel Prize, 1976 (Box-folder 113: 18-20)
  - Portraits taken by Michael Shields, 1976 (Box-folder 113: 21-22)
    Includes negatives.
  - South Africa, 1976 March (Box-folder 113: 23)
  - Occasion, 1976 June (Box-folder 113: 24)
  - Events, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 113: 25)
  - Alaska, 1977 (Box-folder 113: 26)
  - Mont Pélerin Society regional meetings, Taiwan, Chile, and Peru, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 113: 27-28)
  - New Hampshire, 1979 (Box-folder 113: 29)
  - China, 1980 (Box-folder 113: 30)
  - Publicity photos, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 113: 31-32)
  - Free to Choose, 1980, 1990 (Box-folder 113: 33)
  - Madrid, Spain, 1982 (Box-folder 113: 34)
  - Alta, Utah, 1982 (Box-folder 113: 35)
  - Milton and Rose Friedman, 1983 (Box-folder 113: 36)
  - Hawaii, 1983 (Box-folder 114: 1)
  - Slides, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 114: 2)
    Includes Newsweek column slide.
  - Photos from Don Lipsett, circa 1984 (Box-folder 114: 3)
  - Wall Street Week, television program, 1984 (Box-folder 114: 4)
  - United States Military Academy, 1984 September (Box-folder 114: 5)
  - Heritage Dinner with Ronald Reagan, circa 1984 (Box-folder 114: 6)
  - Japan, 1985 (Box-folder 114: 7)
  - Knight seminar, 1985 November (Box-folder 114: 8)
  - Claremont, 1986 (Box-folder 114: 9)
  - Firing Line, Davis, 1986 April 10 (Box-folder 114: 10)
  - Friedman's 75th birthday, 1987 (Box-folder 114: 11)
  - IET Feldberg Institute, 1987 September (Box-folder 114: 12)
  - Beijing, China, 1988 (Box-folder 114: 13)
    Includes postcards.
  - China, 1988 (Box-folder 114: 14)
  - 50th wedding anniversary, 1988 (Box-folder 114: 15)
  - Medal of Freedom, 1988 (Box-folder 114: 16)
  - Freedom conferences, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 114: 17)
  - East-West Center, 1989 (Box-folder 114: 18)
  - Carmel, California, 1990 (Box-folder 114: 19)
  - 25th anniversary of Nobel Prize, Stockholm, Sweden, 1991 (Box-folder 114: 20)
  - Mendocino, California, 1992 (Box-folder 114: 21)
  - Mexico, 1992 (Box-folder 114: 22)
  - Publicity photographs (negatives), 1992 (Box-folder 114: 23)
  - Photographs, 1993 (Box-folder 114: 24)
    Includes photo with Margaret Thatcher.
  - China and Hong Kong trip, 1993 (Box-folder 115: 1)
  - Measuring Economic Freedom conference, 1993 (Box-folder 115: 2)
  - Milton and Rose Friedman, 60th wedding anniversary, 1998 June 18 (Box-folder 115: 3)
  - Photographs for the book Two Lucky People, circa 1988 (Box-folder 115: 4)
    Consists of 13 digitized photographs on one CD-R. Digital use copies are available on computer workstations in the reading room.
    List of photographs: (1) B262C01A - Milton, Stigler, Director, 1947; (2) B262C02A - Rose parents, 1930; (3) B262C03A - Milton and Rose, 1938; (4) B262C04A - Rose, 1918; (5) B262C05A - Milton, parents, and family, 1917; (6) B262C06A - Milton, Rose, Feulner, and Reagan, 1982; (7) B262C07A - Milton, Rose, Edward Teller, Margaret Thatcher, 1995; (8) B262C08A - Milton and Rose, Nobel Ball, 1976; (9) B262C09A - Milton and Rose, Two Lucky People cover; (10) B262C10A - Nixon, Friedman, George Shultz, 1971; (11) B262C11A - Milton, mail at Capital, 1975; (12) B262C12A - Milton 75th and family, 1987; (13) B262C13A - Milton and Rose, Tianamen Square, 1988
  - Photos for autographs hounds, circa 2000 (Box-folder 115: 5)
  - Celebration of 90th birthday, photos with President George W. Bush, Washington, D.C., 2002 (Box-folder 115: 6)
  - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (Box-folder 115: 7-9)
- Incremental Biographical Materials, undated (Boxes 115-123)
  Vitas, personal event materials, professional reports, card files, and clippings. Also contains information on Rose Friedman.
  - Curriculum vita, 1941-1991 (Box-folder 115: 10-12)
  - Class exams, University of Chicago, circa 1932-1939 (Box-folder 115: 13)
  - Faculty reports, University of Chicago, 1963-1978 (Box-folder 115: 14)
  - Activity reports (Hoover Institution, Stanford University), 1979-2002 (Box-folder 115: 15)
  - 75th birthday, 1987 (Box-folder 116: 1)
  - 90th birthday, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 116: 2-3)
  - Obituaries, 2006 (Box-folder 116: 4)